I'm reprogramming a ctu key car right now.
我正在重新设置那张CTU的钥匙卡
Good.
很好
Our couriers are delivering the canisters to the targets.
我的手下正在把毒气罐 送往目的地
They'll be in place soon.
他们很快就能就位
When are you launching your attacks?
你什么时候发动袭击?
After you're done at ctu.
当你搞定CTU之后
When these terrorists attack
当这些恐怖分子发动袭击的时候
you're going to need to maintain order.
你需要维持良好的社会秩序
I believe we should be thinking of a preemptive declaration of martial law.
我认为你应当考虑 在洛杉矶及其周围地区
In the greater los angeles area.
预先宣布戒严
If ctu can't find this man Bierko
如果CTU不能找到那个叫比耶科的人
we're gonna get hit.
我们就会遭到恐怖袭击的
Why didn't you just tell me you were alive?
你为什么不告诉我你还活着?
If you knew I was alive
如果你知道我活着
you would have been at risk
你早就有危险了
and I had no choice.
我别无选择
I'm happy that you're alive I am
我很高兴得知你还活着... 没错 是这样
but I can't give you what you want right now.
但是我不能立即给你想要的一切
Michelle's murder was part of a bigger plan.
米歇尔遇害是个大阴谋的一部分...
To supply terrorists with sentox nerve gas.
向恐怖分子提供Sentox神经毒气
Who's behind it?
是谁主使的?
Christopher Henderson.
克里斯托夫・亨德森
Whatever he's not telling us is important.
他试图隐瞒的消息非常重要
And he's willing to tolerate an inhuman amount of pain.
而他宁愿忍受非人所能承受的痛苦
Thousands of lives are at stake.
成千上万条生命危如累卵
There is enough time for you to tell me
你还有足够的时间来告诉我
what I need to know to stop this insanity please.
阻止这个疯子的办法 告诉我
I'm sorry guy
我很抱歉 伙计
but I can't tell you what you want to know.
但是我不能告诉你  你想知道的事情
this is bauer.
我是鲍尔
We've been compromised.
我们被渗透了
Someone used a stolen key card to access ctu less than an hour ago.
有人在不到一小时之前 拿偷来的钥匙卡进入了CTU
Freeze.
不许动
Drop the gun.
放下枪
Bill it's Jack.
比尔 我是杰克
I think he tried to deploy nerve gas throughout the building.
我想他是要在这幢楼里施放神经毒气
Code six everybody out.
6号警报 所有人撤退
Go go.
快走 快走
Seal all the rooMs.
密封所有房间
Oh no.
不是吧
My god.
我的天
Chloe.
科洛依
The following takes place between 7Pm and 8Pm
以下是发生于傍晚7点至8点之间的故事
Atention all ctu personnel.
所有CTU工作人员注意了
This facility has been contaminated with sentox vx-1 nerve gas.
这座大楼已经被Sentox VX-1型神经毒气所污染
Repeat: This facility has been contaminated.
重复一遍: 这座大楼已经被污染
There are two safe zones on the main floor
底楼有两个安全区域...
the situation room and medical.
局势研究室和医务室
On the second floor
在二楼
the safe zones are the CTU direct's office and holding room four.
安全的区域是CTU主管办公室和4号拘留室
These areas will remain sealed
在化学反应小组到达之前
pending the arrival of the chemical response team.
这些区域会保持密封
If you are in any of these sealed areas
如果你在这些密封区域之中
do not attempt to leave until the crt clears the environment.
请不要试图离开  等待化学反应小组清理现场
I'm on my way
我正赶过去
but it could take 20 to 30 minutes to
但是召集所需要的化学反应小组
gather all the crt personnel you'll need.
成员可能要花20到30分钟
I understand curtis
我能理解 柯蒂斯
but we need crt here now.
但是我们现在就需要 化学反应小组过来
This is a high priority.
这是最先需要解决的
Get here as fast as you can.
尽快赶过来
All right copy
好的 明白...
I'll call you in a few minutes with updates
我几分钟后会汇报最新情况的
this is bauer.
我是鲍尔
Jack it's Bill.
杰克 我是比尔
I just talked to curtis.
我刚打给柯蒂斯
He's with the chemical response team.
他和化学反应小组在一起
They won't be able to get here for at least 30 minutes.
最快要30分钟才能赶到
Why not?
为什么?
Most of their units were sent to Tyler Memorial.
大部分的小组被分配去泰勒医院了
The rest are en route to high probability targets.
其余的人在去其他高危目标的路上
Okay we're going to keep working here.
好吧  我们要在这里继续工作
Our networks are still up right?
我们的网络还通着吧?
Yeah the phones are working the computers are up.
是的 电话还能工作 电脑也能运行
I can coordinate with division from here.
我可以从这儿分区协调
What do you need where you are?
你那里需要什么?
I need to know if Henderson still alive.
我要知道亨德森是否还活着
Where is he?
他在哪儿?
Agent burke was trsferring him over to the isolation clic in medical.
伯克特工正把他送往临床隔离病房
I don'know if they made it before the barriers went down.
不知道他们有没有在隔离开始前到达
You can tell if you pull up a building grid.
连上大楼网络就知道了
What about ctu's chemical response plan?
可以启用CTU化学反应应急计划吗?
Gas masks are in the armory
防毒面具在军械库
atropine is in medical storage.
阿托品在医疗储藏室
Both areas are contaminated.
这两个区域都被污染了
We can't get to them without being exposed to the gas.
不暴露自己并且获得设备是不可能的
Bill I'm going to have to get right back to you.
比尔 我一会儿打给你
Chloe...
科洛依...
I know how difficult this is for you right now
我知道现在你的心情相当糟糕
but there's nothing we can do for him.
但是我们什么都不能为他做了
I need you to come back to work.
我需要你回来继续工作
Well at least tell me how to pull up a building grid.
至少告诉我怎么连接大楼网络
I'll do it myself.
我自己来
Jack we can try to pull it up.
杰克 我们可以试着连接来
Get started.
开始
Chloe ctu is immobile right now.
科洛依 CTU现在需要
Everything is going to go through comm.
将一切维持正常运作
That's you.
只有你能办到
I need you back at work.
我需要你回来工作
I can't.
我不行
Yes you can.
你行的
No I can't.
不 我不干了
Mr. Bauer.
鲍尔先生
What?
干嘛?
I can help her.
我能帮她
I'm a clinical psychologist.
我是个临床心理学家
Thank you.
谢谢你
Chloe
科洛依
my name is Dr. Landes.
我是兰德斯医生
Now he was a friend of yours
他是你的朋友...
what was his name?
他叫什么名字?
Edgar.
埃德加
I'd like you to turn away from edgar and focus on me please.
我要你把注意力从埃德加身上转回来 集中在我身上
Chloe you're in shock
科洛依 你受到了惊吓
and I'd like to help you through it.
我能帮你克服掉
The only thing I'm going to ask you to do is sit in this chair
我只会要求你做一件事  坐在这张椅子上来
and collect your breath.
慢慢呼吸
Let's do that now.
按我教你的
just for a second.
保持一小会儿
He was such a good guy.
他是个好人
I just treated him like crap all day.
我却整天对他大呼小叫
This is my fault.
都是我的错
Sir?
长官?
Someone stole my key card and used it to get into the building.
有人偷了我的钥匙卡 用它进入了大楼
It was missing
它不见了
and I didn't say anything.
而我什么都没说
Why not?
为什么不说?
I thought they just stole my wallet for the money.
我以为他们只是要偷我钱包里的钱
How could you not report it?
你怎么能不汇报呢?
I was embarrassed.
我很尴尬
I didn't want anyone to know I got beat up.
我不想让任何人知道我被打了
So we're all going to die
所以因为你要面子
because you were embarrassed?
我们就得陪葬?
Mr. Almeida what are you doing?
阿尔梅达先生 你要干什么?
I want to know what's going on.
我要知道发生了什么事
No I can't allow that.
不 我不能让你这么做
I'm not sitting in this damn bed while ctu is under attack
我不能在CTU受到攻击的时候 睡在这该死的床上
got it?
明白吗?
Fine.
好吧
How long are we supposed to be sectioned off like this?
我们还要在这里隔离多久?
I haven't received any news.
我还没有收到任何消息
Oh my god.
噢 我的天
Jack we've got the building grid.
杰克 我们已经连接大楼网络了
Buchanan.
我是布坎南
Bill it's Jack
比尔 我是杰克
the grid's up.
网络连接来了
All right
很好
check the isolation zones that have logged in.
检查已经登陆的隔离区
You'll have survivors.
你就能获知生还者了
Two zones have logged on in medical.
医护室有两个区域登陆了
Try them.
试试联络它们
I'm going to keep this line open.
我在线等着
Okay hold on.
好的 等着
Clinic.
临床区
Dr. Besson it's Jack bauer.
本森医生 我是杰克・鲍尔
Jack what's going on?
杰克 发生什么事了?
One of the terrorists infiltrated ctu
有一个恐怖分子潜入了CTU
and deployed a canister of sentox nerve gas through the ventilation system.
通过通风系统散布了sentox神经毒气
That's why we needed to seal off as many rooms as possible.
所以我们要尽可能封锁所有的房间
I need to know if agent burke got to medical with Henderson.
我要知道伯克特工 有没有把亨德森送到医疗中心
Yes he did.
是的 他送到了
Henderson's here right now?
亨德森现在在这儿?
Tony is that you?
托尼 是你吗?
Jack how much longer are we going to be locked down?
杰克 我们还要被封锁多久?
Right now we're in standby
现在 我们在待命
we're trying to figure out how to clean out the air supply.
我们正在想办法清理毒气源
Dr. Besson?
本森医生?
Tony.
托尼
T me a security feed over at medical.
给我看医疗区的安全监视器
Jack I don't think this program is set ufor that.
杰克 我认为这个程序做不到
Try a redirect.
试试改变方向
All ght.
好的
Dr. Besson.
本森医生?
What are you doing?
你要干吗?
Move aside.
靠边站
All right, I've got a video.
好了 画面有了
My god he's got a gun.
天 他有枪
Patch me through to their intercom.
接通房间里的对讲机
Do it.
快
We'll be able to hear them
我们可以听见他们说话
but they can't hear us yet.
但他们还听不到我们说话
You can't kill him.
你不能杀他
He's got information we need.
他有我们需要的情报
He killed my wife.
他杀了我妻子
Tony please don't kill him.
托尼 别杀他 还不能
Move aside Rick.
靠边 瑞克
I don't want to shoot you but I will.
我不想向你开枪 但是我会的
Move it.
靠边
You remember me?
知道我是谁不?
My name is Tony Almeida.
托尼・阿尔梅达
You killed my wife Michelle dessler this morning.
今天早上 你杀了我妻子 米歇尔・戴斯勒
He's going to kill him hurry.
他要杀人了 快
Hurry.
快
She was my life
她是我的生命
and you took her.
而你夺走了她
And now I'm going to take yours.
现在 我要夺走你的
I got it.
接通了
Tony it's Jack.
托尼 我是杰克
I've got you on the security feed.
我从监视器里看到你了
Stay out of this Jack.
不要插手 杰克
Tony please just listen to me.
托尼 别这样 你听我说
You can't do this.
你不能这么做
I know how you feel right now.
我知道你现在的感受
I lost terry the exact same way
就和我失去泰瑞是一样
to one of our own.
失去一个我们最重要的人
I know what it feels to be betrayed like this.
我知道 这就像是背叛
But Tony
但是 托尼
Henderson has information that can save thousands and thousands of lives.
亨德森的情报能拯救很多很多人的生命
And I know that doesn't make you feel better right now
而且我知道那样... 也不能让你现在感到好受些
but I know you Tony.
但是我了解你 托尼
I know you don't want to make this situation any worse than it is.
我知道你不想让局势变得比现在更糟
Please?
你说呢
Please just let us finish our interrogation.
先让我们完成审讯
Hurry up.
快点
Agent burke please continue.
伯克特工 请继续
We have to get him talking.
我们要让他开口
He's our only lead to Bierko and the rest of the sentox canisters
他是唯一能带我们找到 其他神经毒气罐
and how we can find Bierko.
和比耶科的人
Tell me where to find Bierko.
告诉我比耶科藏在哪
Where?
哪里?
Nowhere.
没哪里
What is your computer password?
你的电脑密码是什么?
No.
没密码
I know no password.
我不知道密码
Agent burke can we increase the dose
伯克特工 我们能增加剂量吗?
Not without killing him.
那会杀了他的
Okay take a short break and then start again.
好吧 休息一会儿 再开始
Get back to me as soon as you've got anything.
你有了任何消息马上通知我
Yes sir.
是的 长官
How could ctu have been hit?
CTU怎么会被攻击呢？
We're not sure Mr. Vice president.
我们还不确定 副总统阁下
Are you telling me they didn't have any safeguards in place?
你是在告诉我 他们没有任何防卫措施吗?
They had partial containment
他们有局部防卫措施
but our early reports indicate that 40% of their personnel have been taken out
但是我们早前的报告显示 40%的工作人员已经牺牲
You mean they've been killed?
你意思是他们都被杀了?
We're afraid so sir.
恐怕是这样 阁下
Ctu is protecting this city.
CTU是这座城市的卫士
Are you saying they're no longer capable of doing that?
你是不是说他们现在已经没有能力做好本职工作了?
I'm saying they've been seriously compromised yes.
我是在说他们已经陷入了严重的危机中 是的...是这样
So what are we going to do Ms. Hayes?
那么我们要做什么 海因斯女士?
We've got terrorists with nerve gas canisters out there.
还有恐怖分子拿着神经毒气
Who is going to stop them?
谁去阻止他们?
Mr. President I suggest an emergency restructuring.
总统阁下 我建议紧急改组
Meaning what?
什么意思?
Meaning that the chemical response team will go in neutralize the nerve gas at ctu
意思是化学反应小组 会去清除CTU的神经毒气
and I will take a team in there and personally manage the operation.
我将带领一个小组去那儿  亲自指挥行动
How soon can you do that?
那样做要多久?
Within the hour.
一小时内
Fine. Do it.
很好 去做吧
Yes sir.
是的 长官
All right they're still somewhat operational. It's not a complete disaster.
他们还能控制局势 还不完全是场灾难
Mr. President it is.
总统阁下 这够灾难的了
I can see no other option right now
我们没有其他选择了
but to impose martial law on the city of los angeles.
只有戒严整个洛杉机
Hal my advisors believe if the military takes over the streets
哈尔 我的顾问说 如果军队上街去...
and starts detaining people it could create mayhem.
开始抓人 会造成恐慌的
Sir it's only a matter of time before me canisters are released
阁下 这只是时间问题
in public places and then you will have mayhem.
毒气在公众场所泄露的话 就该你恐慌了
Except without the soldiers you'll need to contain it.
即使军队出动 你也要忍耐一下
So what do I tell the public?
那我要怎么跟公众交代?
That we've got nerve gas canisters all over the city
告诉他们现在整个城市 到处到是神经毒气罐
but we don't know where they are? .
而我们不知道它们在哪?
No no you don't have to get into that.
不 不 不用这么做
Tie it to that earlier incident at the airport.
就说是因为之前机场的事故吧
I'm going to get resistance from all sides.
我会被各方质问的
That's true sir.
是的 先生
We may have to swallow some saltwater but wouldn't it be worth it
我们也许只能自吞苦水了 不过还是值得的
if we can keep the people off the streets
如果我们可以让大家不要上街
safe from another public attack?
避免另一场公开袭击?
I don't know Hal.
我不知道 哈尔
Sir consider this
先生 想想看...
if we clear the streets of everybody except the military
如果我们把部队以外的人 都清出街道的话
these terrorists won't be able to move as freely as they are right now.
这些恐怖分子也不能 再像现在一样行动自如
We have to do whatever we can to stop the people behind this.
我们必须想尽一切办法 阻止幕后黑手
Ctu is no longer an obstacle.
CTU已经不是障碍了
At least for the time being.
至少现在不是
Good.
很好
Have our men move from their current positions and go to the new target.
通知我们的人向新目标进发
How much of the nerve gas will they release there?
这次放多少毒气?
All of it.
全部
Excuse me.
让下
Chloe are you ready to go back to work?
科洛依 准备好回来工作了吗?
What do you need?
你要干什么?
I need you. We can't break Henderson.
我需要你 我们没法让亨德森开口
I need you to keep trying to decrypt the files that we took from his computer.
我要你继续破解我们 从他电脑里弄来的文件
I already tried that. It didn't work. Maybe somebody else could do it.
我已经试过了 没用 也许谁能弄吧
Chloe you're the only person in the room qualified.
科洛依 这个房间里只有你可以
Chloe please. Don't shut down on me now.
科洛依 别这样 现在别打击我了
I'm upset about everything that's happening too
我也对发生的一切感到很难过
but you know how things work around here.
但你知道现在这的情况
We do not quit until it's over.
在这一切结束前 我们没法出去
You're not helping her. You're just making things worse.
你这不是在帮她 只是弄得更糟
I am sure that you are qualified to
我知道你是专业人士...
help someone through this kind of distress over an extended period of time
帮助人们通过一段时间来走出悲伤
but you see we do not have an extended period of time.
但你知道  我们现在没有多余的时间了
So if you don't mind stepping aside so I can do my job I would appreciate it.
所以如果你不介意站在一边 让我干活的话 非常感谢
Believe it or not Jack you don't have to be qualified to help people.
不管你是否相信 杰克 帮助人不需要你专业...
You just have to be there for them.
你只要在他们身边就可以了
Like you were there for my daughter.
就像你在我女儿身边一样
What does that mean?
什么意思?
You're 20 years older than she is.
你比她要大20岁
I know exactly what you're doing.
我很清楚你在干什么
I've done nothing but try and help her deal with her loss.
我没做什么事 只是试着 帮她走出悲伤而已
How dare you accuse me of taking advantage of her.
你怎么可以说 我在占她便宜
You did...
你是在...
dad stop. You can be angry at me all you want
爸爸 停下 要生气你就找我
but before I met barry I didn't want to live. Do you understand that?
但遇到巴里之前 我已经不想活了 你明白吗?
Fine I'll get back to work if everyone could just relax.
好吧 我回来工作 只要你们别再吵了
Jack we have a problem.
杰克 我们有麻烦了
What?
怎么了?
Chloe I just saw the alarm. What's going on?
科洛依 我看到在闪警告 怎么了?
The seal pressure indicators in the contaminated zones
污染区域的密封压力指示器
are showing traces of sublimated polymer near the partition seal.
显示在密封条附近有聚合反应的趋向
What does that mean?
那是什么意思?
It means that the nerve gas must be mixed with a corrosive agent an acid.
意思说神经毒气正在和一种腐蚀剂 混合成一种酸
The acid's breaking down the seal between the rooMs.
这种酸正在侵蚀房间的密封条
How long till the seal fails completely?
密封条还能坚持多久?
It's hard to say for sure.
很难说
Can you give me an estimate?
给我个大概时间好吗?
It's deteriorating quickly. I'd say 15 minutes 20 at the most.
损坏得很快 我想大概15 最多20分钟
And then what?
然后呢?
As soon as the gas permeates the seal it enters the room. Then it's over.
毒气一透过密封条 进了房间 就结束了
Get me schematics on all the isolated zones.
给我所有区域的平面图
Mr. Vice president with all due respect
副总统阁下 恕我直言
I'm not trying to usurp your position.
我不是想取代您的位置
I'm simply trying to serve the president the best way I can.
我只是想尽我的绵薄之力 帮助总统而已
Yes sir.
是的 阁下
What was that about?
怎么了?
I was trying to convince Gardner
我想说服加德纳尔
to let me help him draft the president's statement.
让我代替他起草总统的声明
Charles is letting Hal write his statement?
查尔斯让哈尔给他写声明?
He's insisted.
他坚持要这么做
And the president gave him the go-ahead.
总统让他这么干
But that means Gardner is effectively making policy.
可是这样加德纳尔 就完全可以操纵决定了
We've got to stop him.
我们要阻止他
I'm trying.
我在努力
But you know what kind of pressure the president's under today.
但你知道今天总统的压力有多大
He wants all the counsel he can get.
他需要所有能得到的建议
And Hal's only too eager to help out.
哈尔只是太着急想帮忙而已
Of course he's too eager. He's got his eye on the oval office.
他当然着急 他可是一直盯着总统办公室
Anything he can do to speed up Charles' down fall
任何能够加速查尔斯下台的事情
puts him one step closer to the presidency
都让他一步步靠近总统的位置
Martha you have to intervene.
玛莎 你必须得插手
Hal feeds the president ideas.
哈尔在左右总统的决定
We saw it at the WTO we saw it in Chicago. When they work.
WTO谈判的时候我们看到了 芝加哥的时候也是
Hal takes the credit for them.
好的时候 是哈尔的功劳
When they don't the president takes the hits.
不好的时候 是总统的过错
Have you reminded Charles of that?
你没有提醒过查尔斯吗?
I can't. Hal's the vice president.
我不能 哈尔是副总统
I'm just the chief of staff.
我只是参谋长
You have influence that supercedes any constitutional rank.
你的影响力超过任何实权人物
And now's the time to use it.
现在是用武之时了
I want to see the statement as soon as it's issued.
我要在声明发布后马上看到它
You will.
你会的
I just checked the readings from all uncontaminated zones.
我刚检查了一下无污染区的指数
The testing you've been doing in your respective areas is consistent.
和你们各自区域的检查情况一样
The sentox nerve gas that was released into
周围环境里的神经毒气
the air duct system contains a corrosive agent
正在发生某种化学反应
that is eating away at the barrier seals protecting the safe zones.
腐蚀蚀隔离区房间的密封条
I'm not going to pull any punches.
我没有夸大事实
Crt will not be here to help us.
化学反应小组现在帮不了我们
At this point our only hope is to help ourselves.
基于这点  我们唯一的希望只有全力自救
We need to find a way to either neutralize
我们要想办法中和毒气
or flush the sentox out of the contaminated areas
或者把污染区的毒气排掉
before the barrier seals fail and the gas enters the safe zones.
在密封条失效... 毒气进入安全区之前
I want all personnel working on this problem.
我要所有的人都来想法解决这个问题
We don't have much time. Do what you can.
我们没有多少时间 大家尽力
We'll hope for the best.
希望是最好的结果
Maybe we can do something from in here.
也许我们有办法...
Access the ventilation system?
进入通风系统?
Even if I could it doesn't mean
即使我可以进取
we could do anything to stop the seals from breaking down.
也没法阻止密封条被腐蚀
Just try.
试试
Maybe it's not as bad as we think. Maybe the numbers are off.
也许并不像我们想得这么糟 也许指标出错了
They're not.
没有错
Even if the seals leak crt could get here in time.
即使密封条泄漏了 化学反应小组也会准时到的
The only reason she's here is because I asked her to stay.
是我让她呆在这的
If something happens to her it's going to be because of me...
如果发生什么事 都是因为我...
Because of what I did.
因为我所做的一切
There was no way that you could know that ctu was vulnerable.
你也不知道CTU会被攻击
Jack.
杰克
You've got something?
发现什么了?
I think if I can slow the seals from breaking down
我想我可以减缓密封条的腐蚀
I can flush the contaminated areas using the air conditioning.
我可以用空调把污染区的毒气排出
Do it.
做吧
Something's wrong. The control isn't responding.
有错误 控制系统没有响应
Why not?
为什么?
It's being blocked by some program that I can't get to remotely.
有某些程序让我不能远程连接
It's probably on a computer near holding four.
有可能在4号区附近的一台电脑上
Can you get me how can I get in there?
能告诉我怎么过去吗?
This is a false wall. The air in there is not contaminated.
这是一堵空心墙 里面的空气没有污染
Can he get to the computer through there?
他能通过那到达电脑吗?
Yes but once he makes it through the safe zone he'll be in a contaminated area.
是的 但到安全区域前 他会先暴露在污染区里
What are you talking about? He can't go through a contaminated area.
你们在说什么? 他不能通过污染区
I can hold my breath.
我可以摒住呼吸
The sentox won't be absorbed by my skin over that short a period of time.
短时间内毒气不会通过我的皮肤吸收
As long as I don't in hale it I'll be fine.
只要我不吸气 就没事
Jack you can't hold your breath that long.
杰克 你不可能摒这么久
I only have to hold my breath long enough to get to the computer
我只要在到那计算机之前 摒住呼吸就可以了
disconnect the program and get back to the ventilated room.
关闭程序 然后回到安全区
Once I'm back in the safe room how long will it take you to clear out the sentox
我回到安全区后 你需要多久来清除毒气
About 20 seconds based on the cubic footage.
大概每立方英尺需要20秒
Jack even if you get to the computer what if we can't ventilate that room
杰克 即使你到达那计算机 我们不能给房间排气怎么办?
Chloe thinks we can.
科洛依认为可以
Right now this is our only option. Crt is not going to get here in time.
化学反应小组不能及时赶到 现在 这是我们唯一的选择了
The seals are now 80% gone.
密封条已经被腐蚀了80%
What's the bottom line?
还能坚持多久?
We have less than 20 minutes.
不超过20分钟
All right Jack Chloe and i are on channel one.
好吧 杰克 科洛依和我在一号线
If you need to communicate with anyone else we'll patch you through.
如果你要和其他人通话 我们会给你转过去
As soon as I go through you have to replace this behind me.
我一走 你马上把这堵上
Jack it's time. Go now.
杰克 是时候了 现在快去
Now.
现在
Chloe it's Jack.
科洛依 我是杰克
I just completed the airlock.
我刚封住了入气口
I'm getting ready to move into the ventilation room.
现在准备进入通风区
I'll tap my com unit three times when I'm back in the safe room.
重回安全室后我会敲三下通讯耳机
All right.
好的
Jack I don't have to remind you if that airlock leaks
杰克 我想不用提醒你也知道 如果入气口泄露...
we'll all be dead within the next three minutes.
三分钟内我们都得完蛋
It's not going to leak Chloe.
不会泄露的 科洛依
Okay...
好了
- I'm going in. - Okay.
- 我要进去了  - 好
seal corrosion is now at 86 percent.
密封条已被侵蚀86%
Is there anything we can do from here?
我们在这里能做点什么吗
No we just have to wait.
只能等待
There's nothing we can do to get your dad out any faster.
无论我们做什么... 都不能让你爸爸更快出来
Don't talk down to me Chloe.
别用那种语气跟我讲话 科洛依
Listen we're in a crisis situation here okay?
听着 我们现在处于危机之中
Tempers are bound to flare. Let's just everybody breathe.
大家火气都不小  调节一下呼吸吧
What's with you and the breathing?
呼吸又呼吸
Is that your solution to everything?
万能又无敌 是不?
It's Jack he's back in the room.
是杰克 他回到那间房间了
It's too soon he couldn't have found the program and disabled it yet.
这也太快了 他不可能这么快...  找到程序 更别说中止了
He's got 15 more seconds before the room clears.
还有十五秒室内空气才能净化
What's it mean that he finished so quickly?
"这也太快了 "是什么意思?
I don't know.
不知道
Well it could be a good thing right?
这是好事吧
It should be a good thing or it could be a bad thing.
你是文盲? 所谓"不知道"的意思
That's what "I don't know" means.
就是说可能好也可能糟
All right Jack the room is clear you can breathe. Are you okay?
好了杰克 空气净化完成 你可以呼吸了 还好吗?
I couldn't get to it.
我到不了那里
Chloe you're right. I saw it.
科洛依 你说对了  我看见了
There's a computer program running on the ac control unit
有个程序在电流控制台运行
but there's a security grate in the wall behind the vent.
但墙上通风口后安装了防护网
I don't see it on my system.
系统上看不见
Trust me it's there.
相信我 有的
I just found it.
刚刚看见
It was a security upgrade in the last two years.
是前两年安装的安全升级装置
Somebody didn't file it properly that's why I didn't see it.
肯定有人备份文件时疏忽了 所以我刚才没有看见
Are there any other vents that could help us get into that wall?
还有别的通风口让我进去吗
No they've all been upgraded.
没有 都加安全门了
Well it's a room there's got to be a door. Where does it lead?
那是个房间 门通向哪里?
To a corridor above holding four.
通向4号禁闭室的走廊
None of us can get there from where we're at.
在这里没人能过去
Who's in holding room four?
谁在4号禁闭室
Lynn Mcgill.
林・麦克基尔
Are there any other vented rooms we can get him to?
还有哪些通风室可以让他过去?
No Jack there's nothing.
没了 杰克 一个都没有
Patch me through to him.
帮我接通他
Mcgill here.
我是麦克基尔
Lynn it's Jack.
林 我是杰克
We found a computer interrupt in the ac control unit.
我们在电流控制台发现阻挡程序
Now if we can shut that down in the next few minutes
现在如果能在几分钟内将其解除
we can stop the gas from permeating the safe zones.
就能防止毒气蔓延至安全区
Well that's good news.
这是好消息
The problem is you're the only person close enough to get to it.
问题是... 你是唯一能够接近控制台的人
Chloe?
科洛依?
It's directly above the holding room where you are now.
就在你所在禁闭室的上层
Take the stairs
上楼梯
go to the left around the corner. It's the room on your left.
拐弯左转 左手边的房间
Okay...
好...
how are we going to do this Jack?
该怎么做 杰克?
Lynn the truth is if I can get there
林 要是我能自己去
I would do this myself but I'm not close enough.
我就亲自做了 可我靠近不了
No one who's still alive in ctu is. You're the only person who can do this.
CTU里活着的人里  只有你能这样做了
And I'm going to have to ask you to do it without any protection.
而且我要求你在... 没有任何保护的情况下去做
I see.
明白了
No you don't.
不 你不明白
As soon as you open the door to the hallway your room will become contaminated.
你一打开通向走廊的门  你的房间就会被毒气污染
You can hold your breath long enough to fix the problem
你可以摒住呼吸 去把问题解决掉
but we have nowhere else to send you.
同时你也就无路可走了
We can't airlock you.
无法再将你隔离
There are two of us in here Jack.
我们这里有两个人 杰克
Sir this is Harry Swinton.
长官 我是哈里・史文顿
So you're saying that if he does this then we're both gonna die?
你的意思是如果他这样做 我们就都得丧命?
I'm so sorry.
很遗憾
We don't have a choice Harry.
我们别无选择 哈里
How do we know that you're not just making this story up
我们怎么知道 你是不是在胡编乱造...
so you don't have to make the sacrifice yourself?
来保全自己性命
You don't.
别这么想
All I can ask you to do is believe me. I'm telling you the truth.
我请求你相信我 我没有说谎
Well that's easy for you to say sir. You're not the one who's about to die.
哼 你说得轻巧  要去送命的又不是你
It's not easy for me to say.
我说得并不轻巧
Hold on.
等等
We have to do this Harry.
我们必须得去 哈里
We're going to die anyway.
横竖都是死
If we don't so will everyone in ctu.
我们不去 CTU里每个人都得丧命
We have to do this.
我们必须得去
Okay Jack go ahead.
杰克 说吧 怎么做
Once you enter the ventilation room
进入通风室后
the computer will be on your right.
电脑在你们右边
There's a program running on the computer.
电脑上有一个程序在运行
You need to quit out of it I'll take it from there.
你们得让把它终止 剩下的我来做
Lynn we don't have a lot of time.
林 我们时间不多了
I'll do it.
照你说的办
Chloe...
科洛依...
I'm sorry about how I acted earlier...
我为刚才所作所为道歉
and about yo friend that died.
也为你死去的朋友感到遗憾
Okay. Thanks.
没事 谢谢
I've been wanting to ask you something.
我一直想问你
Did you have contact with my dad while he was gone?
我爸爸失踪时你跟他联系过吗?
I sent him information about once a month.
我每个月都给他发一次信息
What kind of information?
什么信息?
A lot of different things.
许多不同的事情
About me?
关于我吗?
Actually almost all of it was about you.
事实上 绝大部分是关于你
Your breakup with chase your depression...
你跟蔡斯分手 你得了抑郁症...
wha... ?  How did you get... ?
什么? 你怎么知道...?
I'm really good at getting information.
搜集信息是我的特长
I don't judge it I just pass it on.
我从不对此作评论 我只是负责传话
I'm sorry about you and chase. It must've been really painful.
对于你和蔡斯分手我很遗憾  你当时一定很痛苦
Yeah it was.
是 是这样
So you talked to him too?
你跟他谈过?
Chase?  No.
蔡斯? 没有
You know where he is?
你知道他在哪里?
No but I could find out if you want.
不 不过你想知道我会去查
No no it's all right.
不必了
Barry thinks I shou let that go.
巴里认为我应该忘记这件事
He's probably right.
也许他是对的
Yeah well shrinks are always giving advice
对的 说三道四是心理医生的特长
that they probably don't follow themselves.
不过 他们连自己说的都不相信
How are you doing?
你过得怎样?
Well this morning woke up with a guy in my bed
早上还睡在我床上的人
that I'll probably never see again.
可能以后再也见不到了
And I just watched one of my best friends die right in front of me
还有刚刚... 我最好的朋友就在我面前死去
so... I guess not that great.
所以... 我想并不好
Yeah.
恩
Replace the panel.
封好面板
Pull up the security feed for the observation room.
打开观察室监视器
You be a good girl for mommy okay?
做妈妈的乖女儿 好吗?
She tells you you have to go to bed you have to go to bed.
她让你去睡觉 你就去
When you coming home?
你什么时候回家?
I don't know honey.
我也不知道 宝贝
If I fall asleep will you wake me up?
要是我睡着了 你会叫醒我吗?
Of course I will.
当然
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
- 真的吗?  - 真的
I'm going in now Harry.
我要进去了 哈里
Say good-bye.
说再见吧
I love you.
我爱你
Love you to daddy.
我也爱你 爸爸
Bye baby girl.
宝贝女儿 再见了
Chloe we're ready.
科洛依 我们准备完毕
I'm going in.
我要进去了
Okay good luck. And thanks for doing this.
好运 谢谢你们所做的
Yeah.
好
He did it.
他做到了
Is the ac responding?
电流有反应了吗?
Yes. I'm starting the fans now.
是 我正在启动换气扇
How long before the sentox is neutralized?
中和神经毒气需要多长时间?
At least 15 minutes but the concentration should go down enough to stop
至少15分钟 但是浓度可以降低到防止...
eating away at the seals immediately.
密封条被腐蚀的程度
Polymer count is down
聚合物指数下降
it looks like the seals will hold until all zones are clear.
看起来所有区域清理完毕前密封条仍有效
Lynn Harry I don't know if you can still hear me
林 哈里 不知你们是否能够听见 如果听见的话...
but I want you to know what you did was successful.
不过我还是想让你们知道... 你们成功了
The seals are holding.
密封条保住了
I will personally notify your familiesand tell them of the sacrifice you made.
我会亲自告诉你们的家属 你们所做出的牺牲
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
I don't know what else to say.
我不知道该再说什么
Thank you.
谢谢
I'm okay...
我还活着...
I'm okay.
我还活着
Pull up the security feed to medical.
监视画面转到医务室
Can you hear me?
听见我说话吗?
What's your name?
你叫什么?
No...
不知道...
no name.
没有名字
You're wasting your time.
你在浪费时间
Agent burke this is Jack bauer.
伯克特工 我是杰克・鲍尔
What have you got from Henderson?
亨德森招供没有?
Nothing. He's still not talking.
他什么也不说
Okay keep working on him.
好 继续问他
As soon as the barriers go up I'll get back to you.
隔离解除我马上过去
Chloe
科洛依
I don't think we're going to break Henderson now.
我想现在还撬不开亨德森的嘴
All the information that we're going to get is from his computer.
我们只能从电脑上获取信息了
I need you to keep working on those files.
我希望你继续
Most of my team is gone. How am I going to do that?
我的团队几乎都牺牲了 我怎么干得了?
Only work on his files.
只能继续破译他的档案
Kim
金
as soon as the barriers go up I want you go over to medical
隔离解除 你就去医务室
and let them check you out.
让他们给你检查
No dad when the barriers go up I'm leaving.
不 爸爸 隔离解除 我就走
Kim please just do this for me.
别这样 金 就算为了我
We still need to talk.
我们还需要谈谈
There's nothing to talk about.
没什么可说的了
Don't be in such a hurry to cut me off.
别这么急着拒我于千里...
You cut me off.
是你拒我千里之外
Listen to me I'm not angry.
听我说 我并没生气
I love you.
我爱你
But there's nothing left to say except I don't want to be around you.
但我不想和你一起  没什么好说的了
Every time I am something horrible happens. People die
每次在你身边都会发生可怕的事  都会有人死
and I know that's not your fault but I can't be a part of it.
我知道并不是你的错  但我只是不想卷入其中
I don't want you to be a part of that.
我也不想你被卷进来
All I want is for one day you and I just to be able to spend time together.
我只想有一天能和你在一起过平静的日子
Kim I had to give you up once I'm not going to let that happen again.
金 我曾不得不弃你而去 我保证不会再有下次了
Dad...
爸爸
I can't.
算了
- God that was close. - I know.
- 总算结束了  - 是啊
Are you all right?
还好吗?
No.
不好
An emergency peacekeeping force.
紧急维和部队
It was Hal's suggestion.
哈尔的建议
I think it works.
我想这会有用
Charles
查尔斯
aren't you afraid that an edict of this kind could do far more damage
难道你不怕这种通告会比
than any chemical weapon ever could?
任何化学武器造成更大损失吗?
Martha ctu has been attacked.
玛莎 CTU已经被袭击
Our first line of defense is shut down
我们第一道防线已被击溃
and people were killed because of this chemical weapon.
人们被化学武器夺去生命
And that's just a prelude to what's going to happen in this city
这仅仅是一个序幕
more nerve gas will be released I can guarantee it.
还会有更多神经毒气被释放 我保证
Look if you or Mike you have any better ideas please
如果你是麦克  你会有更好的主意嘛? 拜托
I would be glad to hear them.
如果有 我倒是想听听
- I can break a moment.  - Certenly.
- 能离开会儿吗?  - 当然
What is it martha?
怎么了 玛莎?
If you
如果你...
Charles logan really feel
查尔斯・洛根 真的觉得...
that martial law is your only option
戒严是唯一选择
I will support you.
我会支持你
But what I will not do
但是我不会...
is stand by and watch Hal Gardner use you
坐视哈尔・加德纳尔利用你
to promote his own agenda.
宣传他的议程而不管
Please martha give me some credit.
玛莎 请相信我
He has done it before.
他不是第一次这么做了
He is not the president.
他不是总统
You are.
你才是
I am doing this because it's the right thing to do.
我这么做 因为这是正确选择
I don't know how much more of this I can take
我不知道我还能承受多少
I real don't.
真的不知道
David's assination the nerve gas
大卫被暗杀 神经毒气...
the murder of those hostages walt cummings' betrayal
机场人质牺牲 沃尔特・卡明斯的背叛
and you...
而你...
I almost lost you.
我几乎失去你
I didn't lose you did I?
我没有失去你 对不?
No Charles.
没有失去
You didn't lose me.
你并没失去我
I'm still here.
我还在
Yes.
讲
Good.
那就好
The men are there. They need the schematics.
人员就位 图纸呢?
Who is it?
是谁啊
Just a client.
一个客户
Yes.
你好
Have you got it yet?
弄到没有?
I told you I'd call you as soon as I have everything.
我告诉过你 办成给你电话
I'm still waiting on a few items.
还差一点
I'm paying you a lot of money Collette.
我可是花了大价钱请你的 科勒特
And if you could have gotten the detailed specs
如果你能从别人那里
of a facility this secure from someone else you would have.
弄到更详细的信息 你早就请别人了
But you didn't.
但你没那么做
You called me and I'll have it for you in a few minutes.
你找了我... 我几分钟之后就能给你弄到
What's wrong?
怎么了?
Nothing.
没什么
Difficult client.
难缠的客户
Wish I knew exactly what it is you did.
我真希望知道你到底在做什么
I might be able to help.
我或许能帮上忙
You do help me.
你帮了我了
Oh I can't.
不行
I have to go and finish something.
我要走了 还有事要忙
Finish this.
就做一次
How long till the air will be safe to breathe?
还要多久 空气才能让人呼吸?
all right thank you very much.
好的 非常感谢
Buchanan.
我是布坎南
Mr. Buchanan this is Karen Hayes from homeland security.
布坎南先生  我是国土安全部的凯伦・海因斯
Karen.
凯伦
I'm running a damage assessment and I need your body count.
我正在统计伤亡情况  我需要你报个数字
We don't have a body count yet.
我们现在还没统计出来
We'll know more when crt gets here and the barriers lift.
等化学反应小组来了 打开防护栏后才能得到确切数字
What's your best estimate?
保守估计是多少?
I'm guessing we'll need at least 20 in comm
我想指挥部至少20人
and 35 in tactical and other departments.
战术部及其他部门35人
All right well I'm on my way over there with a core team.
好的 我和指挥小组在路上
We can make adjustments when I get there.
到了之后就能做出相应决定
You coming here now?
你现在要来?
Yes.
是
I see.
明白了
I'll be there soon.
马上到
How's your progress?
进行得如何?
Good.
没问题
I've already reformatted their main servers to our specs.
我已经重新格式化了他们的主服务器
All their tactical protocols will have to go through me.
他们所有网路管制协定都要经过我手上
Good.
很好
I may have to replace some of their personnel with my people.
我可能得用我自己的一些人手
Do you have a problem with that?
你有意见吗?
Absolutely not.
没问题
After what these people have been through
经过这种折腾
most of them won't be up to full capacity.
大部分人可能都状态欠佳了
We need to identify these people quickly and send them home.
我们得马上找出他们 把他们送回家
What about chain of command?
管理层怎么办?
Am I going to need approval from Bill Buchanan
如果对人事方面进行变动的话
if I want to make a personnel change?
需要经过比尔・布坎南同意吗?
No Bill won't be in charge when we get there
不用 我们到后他就做不了主了
I will.
我负责
For all intents and purposes ctu is no longer an operation entity.
事实上CTU不再是行动实体
It's a building with workers who will report to us.
只是座有人在为我们工作的大楼
We're clear. I'm going back to medical.
可以了 我要回医务室
Kim
金
I have to finish this now.
我现在得完成任务
I know. Good-bye dad.
我知道 再见 爸爸
Good-bye
再见了
Excuse me Jack.
等一下 杰克
I just wanted to say thank you
我只想说 谢谢你...
for saving our lives.
救了我们
I mean we definitely couldn't have gotten through this without you.
没有你 我们肯定撑不过来
Take her outside of the city.
带她到别的城市去
Don't make any stops. You understand?
一刻也别犹豫 明白吗?
Looks like he's dead.
看起来死了
No.
没有
His nervous system is shut down.
他的神经系统崩溃了
Well can you wake him up?
能叫醒他吗?
No.
不行
Almeida.
我是阿尔梅达
Tony it's Jack. I'm on my way.
我是杰克 我马上到
Yeah Jack
好 杰克
Henderson's in a coma. He's not coming out of it.
亨德森昏迷还没苏醒
You've had your chance. He's mine now.
你错过机会了 他现在是我的人了
Damn it Tony just wait until I get there.
妈的 托尼 等我过去
No I'm done waiting.
不 我等够了
You don't want to do this. It's not going to bring back Michelle.
你不会这么做的 因为这样换不回米歇尔
No
不
No but I'll feel better.
起码我会好受一点
Trust me it won't.
相信我 别这么做
You're probably right. I'll let you know.
也许你是对的 我会让你知道
Tony. Tony?
托尼 托尼
What'd Jack say?
杰克说什么了?
He's on his way here.
他正往这里赶
We'll figure out what to do when he gets here.
我们得想想他来了怎么办
There's nothing to figure out.
没什么可想的
This guy's cooked.
这家伙完蛋了
Tony. Tony.
托尼 托尼
I-I couldn't do it.
我下不了手
It's all right. It's all right. Come on.
没事 没事的 撑住
You stay with me. Stay with me.
我在呢 我在
I need help.
我需要帮助
Somebody help.
快来人
No no...
不 不...
No hang on.
坚持住啊
Hang on.
坚持
She's gone Jack.
伙计 她...她走了